<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Email | Chuhan Wang | 王楚涵</title>
    <link>https://wangchuhan.cn/category/email/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://wangchuhan.cn/category/email/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Email</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://wangchuhan.cn/media/icon_hudba5026d243df735440987f9ddc8c7ba_39106_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Email</title>
      <link>https://wangchuhan.cn/category/email/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Large-scale and Longitudinal Measurement Study of DKIM Deployment</title>
      <link>https://wangchuhan.cn/publication/security22/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wangchuhan.cn/publication/security22/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this paper, we provide a large-scale and longitudinal measurement study on how well DKIM is deployed and managed. Our measurement results show that 28.1% of Alexa Top 1 million domains have enabled DKIM, of which 2.9% are misconfigured. We demonstrate that the issues of DKIM key management and DKIM signatures are prevalent in the real world, even for well-known email providers (e.g., Gmail and Mail.ru).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NoSpoofing: &lt;a href=&#34;https://nospoofing.cn/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://nospoofing.cn/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weak Links in Authentication Chains: A Large-scale Analysis of Email Sender Spoofing Attacks</title>
      <link>https://wangchuhan.cn/publication/security21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wangchuhan.cn/publication/security21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This paper systematically analyzes the transmission of an email and identiﬁes a series of new attacks capable of bypassing SPF, DKIM, DMARC and user-interface protections. We conduct a largescale experiment on 30 popular email services and 23 email clients, and ﬁnd that all of them are vulnerable to certain types of new attacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/nospoofing/ehidaopjcnapdglbbbjgeoagpophfjnp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;NoSpoofing&lt;/a&gt;.
We designed a Chrome Extension called NoSpoofing. It is a UI notification scheme which can alert users that the emails they receive may be spoofing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NoSpoofing</title>
      <link>https://wangchuhan.cn/project/nospoofing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wangchuhan.cn/project/nospoofing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NoSpoofing is a UI notification scheme which can alert users that the emails they receive may be spoofing..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email UI rendering is a significant part that affects the users’ perception of an email’s authenticity. However, most of the web mails and email clients we tested do not display SPF, DKIM, or DMARC authentication results explicitly. Thus, it is difficult for ordinary users to fully understand the details of email authentication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An effective defense method is to provide a user-friendly UI notification, which alerts users that the emails they receive may be spoofing. This extension is such an UI notification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Usage: Users can click the icon of the extension when reading an email. Then the web UI will show whether the email is safe or not. If users want to know the details of this email, they can click the notification message.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
